# A. Moh. Fachru' Ridho Abdurrahman

BTN UNTAD Blok D1 No.14, Tondo, Palu, Central Sulawesi

082290584403 | Andifachrurridho@gmail.com

amfa510.github.io/andifachrurridho

#### Informasi Pribadi

I am Andi Muh. Fachru' Ridho Abdurrahman, a graduate of the Information Systems Study Program at the Bina Mulia Palu School of Computer Science Management. I have some experience in building web-based application systems, as well as mastering several programming languages used in Front-end and Back-end development. I also have a special interest in data structures and efficient and structured system development.

# Pengalaman

• PT Media LAB Teknologi

2022 - 2024

Web Developer

- Create and develop websites and web-based applications.
- Design responsive displays to be compatible with all devices.
- Design and manage databases on web-based application or websites.
- Integrate multimedia content on web-based application and websites.
- Test and maintain systems to ensure application and website functionality.

#### PT Tunas Morasi Indonesia

2021 - 2022

### **IT Support**

- Building and managing websites.
- Checking and ensuring all devices are running normally.
- Checking some incoming and outgoing data.
- Ensuring supporting devices such as printers and scanners are operating properly.

## FTIK Institut Agama Islam Negeri Palu

2018 - 2020

Website Admin

- Assisting in the development of the FTIK website
- Maintaining the FTIK website
- Managing data, content, and pages of the FTIK website

## Pendidikan

• Bina Mulia Palu College of Informatics and Computer Management 2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science/Information System (GPA: 3.17 Out of 4.00)

Vocational High School 2 Palu, Central Sulawesi
 Multimedia (82.50)

2013 - 2016

## Keterampilan

- HTML
   MySQL
- CSS
   Bootstrap
- PHPPhotoShop
- Javascript
   MS Office Excel, Word, Powerpoint